<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView OnclickListener</string>
    <string name="title">IT CAREERS</string>

    <string-array name="career_titles">
        <item>Cyber Security</item>
        <item>The Internet Of Things</item>
        <item>Mobile Computing</item>
        <item>Artificial Intelligence</item>
        <item>Machine Learning</item>
        <item>Deep Learning</item>
        <item>Data Engineering</item>
        <item>Software Engineering</item>
        <item>Web Development</item>
        <item>Cloud Engineering</item>
        <item>Robotics Engineering</item>
        <item>Network Engineering</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="career_descriptions">
        <item>Cyber security is the practice of protecting systems, networks, and programs from digital attacks. These cyber attacks are usually aimed at
            accessing, changing, or destroying sensitive information; extorting money from users; or interrupting normal business processes.
                Implementing effective cyber security measures is particularly challenging today because there are more devices than people,
                and attackers are becoming more innovative.</item>

        <item>IoT software engineering refers to the systematic development of IoT infrastructure using a blend of software and hardware solutions.
                IoT software engineering deals with data collected via sensors and processes it to make sense for real-world applications with intuitive
               UI and visual representation</item>

        <item>Mobile computing is human–computer interaction in which a computer is expected to be transported during normal usage,
                 which allows for the transmission of data, voice, and video. Mobile computing involves mobile communication, mobile hardware,
                and mobile software. Communication issues include ad hoc networks and infrastructure networks as well as communication properties,
               protocols, data formats, and concrete technologies. Hardware includes mobile devices or device components. Mobile software deals
               with the characteristics and requirements of mobile applications.</item>

        <item>According to the father of Artificial Intelligence, John McCarthy, it is “The science and engineering of making intelligent machines,
               especially intelligent computer programs”.Artificial Intelligence is a way of making a computer, a computer-controlled robot, or a software
              think intelligently, in the similar manner the intelligent humans think.AI is accomplished by studying how human brain thinks, and how
              humans learn, decide, and work while trying to solve a problem, and then using the outcomes of this study as a basis of developing intelligent
               software and systems.</item>

        <item>Machine learning (ML) is the subset of artificial intelligence (AI) that focuses on building systems that learn—or improve performance—based
                 on the data they consume. Artificial intelligence is a broad term that refers to systems or machines that mimic human intelligence.</item>

        <item>Deep learning (also known as deep structured learning) is part of a broader family of machine learning methods based on artificial neural
               networks with representation learning. Learning can be supervised, semi-supervised or unsupervised.Deep-learning architectures such
                as deep neural networks, deep belief networks, deep reinforcement learning, recurrent neural networks, convolutional neural networks and
                Transformers have been applied to fields including computer vision, speech recognition, natural language processing, machine translation,
                bioinformatics, drug design, medical image analysis, climate science, material inspection and board game programs, where they have produced
              results comparable to and in some cases surpassing human expert performance.Artificial neural networks (ANNs) were inspired by
               information processing and distributed communication nodes in biological systems.ANNs have various differences from biological brains.
               Specifically, artificial neural networks tend to be static and symbolic, while the biological brain of most living organisms is dynamic
               (plastic) and analogue.</item>

        <item>Information engineering, also known as data engineering, information technology engineering or information engineering methodology,
                 refers to the building of systems to enable the collection and usage of data.</item>

        <item>Software engineering is a systematic engineering approach to software development. A software engineer is a person who applies the
                 principles of software engineering to design, develop, maintain, test, and evaluate computer software.</item>

        <item>Web development is the work involved in developing a website for the Internet or an intranet. Web development can range from developing
              a simple single static page of plain text to complex web applications, electronic businesses, and social network services</item>

        <item>Cloud engineering is the application of engineering disciplines to cloud computing. It brings a systematic approach to concerns of
                commercialization, standardization, and governance of cloud computing applications. </item>

        <item>Robotics is an interdisciplinary branch of computer science and engineering. Robotics involves design, construction, operation, and
                use of robots. The goal of robotics is to design machines that can help and assist humans.</item>

        <item>A network engineer is a technology professional who has the necessary skills to plan, implement and oversee the computer networks that
                 support in-house voice, data, video and wireless network services.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>